[{"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Senator, it's almost too much to bear, isn't it, listening?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "You -- there is no Second Amendment right to bear every type of weapon that you know of.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "What do you say to those who say, I have my Second Amendment rights, I'm entitled to bear arms, you are not entitled to take away that right by removing these kind of weapons from the streets and from the stores?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Yes, I hope so, Piers.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "That this may be as some are hoping a tipping point for the American public opinion?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "It's just a fact.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Are you proud of what you said?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, you need to ask the reporter, because he was the one that approached me with the particular questions.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Do you think this is a time to talk about guns being fun when 20 children aged 5 years old are being blown to pieces by a weapon that is freely available in this country?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "We do understand it's not a machine gun.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Why does anybody in America who is not in the military or the police force need a semiautomatic weapon that can unleash hundreds of shots in a matter of a few minutes and slaughter innocent Americans?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Well, automobiles kill more people on our streets than guns do, but we don't say we shouldn't have them because some maniac that's drunk ends up driving a car into a family and killing them.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Why you persist in wanting this to be freely available to Americans?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "You're quite happy with where things are?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, most of it is either suicides or criminal on criminal shootings.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "I don't because the FBI clumps it together with suicides.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Do you know that figure?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Not everyone.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "You think -- so you believe this theory that if everyone in that movie theater was armed, they would have all stood up and shot him?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I believe somebody firing at him would have slowed him down or possibly stopped him, yes.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "How many do you want to be armed in that movie theater?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "And they're highly trained -- yes.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Eleven to 12,000 murders from guns a year in America.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "How many suicides do they have?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Suicides are higher in Japan than they are in America.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "And you still don't care, do you?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "I think it's a multitude of things, Piers.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "But what should that something be?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Yes, I absolutely would.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Would you like to see a ban on both of those things, as Senator Feinstein is trying to push through?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "They're very strong.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "How do you think the community is doing there?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Well, to contribute I think for our country, because it's really about our country, if it's only Newtown that goes through these changes and tries to effect these things, that's one small part.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "And as people are watching this and want to know how they can help, what is the best way for people outside of Newtown to contribute?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I'm slowly recovering.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "How you doing physically, first of all?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, I saw the initial reports like everyone did that maybe just the shooter had been killed.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "What were your feelings when you heard about the scale of what had happened coming so soon after what happened to you?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Yes, that's right.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "You actually live literally 10 minutes away, don't you?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I think it's certainly discouraging in some sense.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "What does this say about America that you're attacked in a movie theater by a young man with an AR-15 assault rifle and then 10 minutes away from where you live, an elementary school is shot up with a young man with exactly the same weapon?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "We were all gathered in Aurora, and we were sitting in the room, waiting for the president to arrive.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "What did he say to you then, Dave, and what happened?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "We are behind them 100 percent.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "What do you say to the parents in Sandy Hook now who are trying to somehow deal with this?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "I say to them it's not about their Second Amendment rights.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "It was an AR-15.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "It was an AR-15?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "No, actually, it's not.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "That's not the correct debate, it is?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "He saw two students killed?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "She was shot dead.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "She was shot dead?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Because I think it really takes somebody in our position, once we've lost somebody, once we've known somebody who is injured and are -- they've got lasting post traumatic stress syndrome, to really see the effects and damages it causes, because it's unfortunately a very unique club.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Why are the Americans so reluctant to collectively rise up and demand action, do you think?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "God, Piers, put me on the spot here.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "If there is one thing you could say to people about guns, what would you say?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "121217pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "How many are children?", "qSentId": 648}]